<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Jose' log</title><link href="http://joseteneb.com/en/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://joseteneb.com/feeds/goals.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://joseteneb.com/en/</id><updated>2016-01-05T19:30:00+00:00</updated><entry><title>Goals 2016</title><link href="http://joseteneb.com/en/metas-2016.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-01-05T19:30:00+00:00</updated><author><name>Jose Teneb</name></author><id>tag:joseteneb.com,2016-01-01:en/metas-2016.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This year I started considering something that I hadn't thought of in previous years. It's more or less a goal list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Jimmy Fallon" src="http://joseteneb.com/en/../images/metas2016.png" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't a big thing, but it's important to me. Anyway, here it is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pass a First Certificate Exam: I came to Ireland a few months ago with the idea of improving my English level. I think sitting for the exam is a good plan to show it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write more: Maybe the most difficult of all. I have always intended to write more, but procrastination usually wins out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel to Iceland: One of my goals last year was to begin this one living in Ireland. Dublin and Iceland are separated by only 1476,14km, barely 10% of the distance between Argentina and Ireland.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in a 5K run: a very clear goal for this year, trendy and with a lot of offer. We'll see what comes out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take more pictures: The last year I took a photography course that led me to understand how take the photographs I want. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Carry out an important proyect: I have projects that I have started and have never finished and others that are just ideas that I have wanted to develop for a while. The point is to get to the end of the year with a project with which I feel plesead and satisfied.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea of making this list here is to track and check how it's going. &lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="goals2016"></category><category term="first-certificate"></category><category term="5km"></category><category term="projects"></category><category term="islandia"></category><category term="photography"></category></entry></feed>